<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "https://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
    <longdescription lang="en">
        Performance Co-Pilot (PCP) provides a framework and services to support system-level performance monitoring and
        management. It presents a unifying abstraction for all of the performance data in a system, and many tools for
        interrogating, retrieving and processing that data.
    </longdescription>
    <maintainer type="person" proxied="yes">
        <email>web@inode64.com</email>
        <name>Fco. Javier Félix</name>
    </maintainer>
    <upstream>
        <remote-id type="github">performancecopilot/pcp</remote-id>
    </upstream>
    <use>
        <flag name="activemq">Enable PCP Performance Metrics Domain Agent (PMDA) for collecting metrics from ActiveMQ
        </flag>
        <flag name="bind">Enable PCP Performance Metrics Domain Agent (PMDA) for collecting metrics from BIND via its
            REST interface
        </flag>
        <flag name="discovery">Support discover PCP services on the network</flag>
        <flag name="doc">Enable building of the PCP books</flag>
        <flag name="infiniband">Support for inifiniband metrics</flag>
        <flag name="influxdb">Customizable performance metrics exporter tool from PCP to InfluxDB</flag>
        <flag name="json">Customizable performance metrics exporter tool from PCP to JSON</flag>
        <flag name="libvirt">Enable PCP Performance Metrics Domain Agent (PMDA) for collecting metrics from libvirt
            virtual machines
        </flag>
        <flag name="nginx">Enable PCP Performance Metrics Domain Agent (PMDA) for collecting metrics from Nginx</flag>
        <flag name="nutcracker">Enable PCP Performance Metrics Domain Agent (PMDA) for collecting metrics from
            NutCracker (TwemCache)
        </flag>
        <flag name="perfevent">Enable PCP Performance Metrics Domain Agent (PMDA) for collecting metrics from hardware
            performance counters using the Linux kernel perf_event API
        </flag>
        <flag name="pie">Build programs as Position Independent Executables (a security hardening technique)</flag>
        <flag name="podman">Enable PCP Performance Metrics Domain Agent (PMDA) for collecting metrics from podman</flag>
        <flag name="postgres">Enable PCP Performance Metrics Domain Agent (PMDA) for collecting metrics about the
            PostgreSQL database
        </flag>
        <flag name="snmp">Enable PCP Performance Metrics Domain Agent (PMDA) for collecting metrics from SNMP</flag>
        <flag name="ssp">Build programs with stack smashing protector</flag>
        <flag name="systemd">Support for systemd services</flag>
        <flag name="xls">Customizable performance metrics exporter tool from PCP to XLSX</flag>
    </use>
</pkgmetadata>
